export default data = [
  {
    question: 'Who won the FIFA World Cup 2022?',
    options: ['Argentina', 'France', 'Brazil'],
    correct_option: 'Argentina'
  },
  {
    question: 'A soccer match consists of parts called:',
    options: ['Set', 'Period', 'Halftime', 'Game'],
    correct_option: 'Halftime'
  },
  {
    question: 'How long is a soccer half, in minutes?',
    options: ['45', '20', '90', '40'],
    correct_option: '45'
  },
  {
    question: 'Organizer of the FIFA World Cup:',
    options: ['Olympic Organizing Committee', 'NHL', 'FIFA', 'Coca-Cola'],
    correct_option: 'FIFA'
  },
  {
    question:
      'This striker is recognized as the best soccer player on the planet. Three-time world champion. This Brazilian national team player is known as:',
    options: ['Luiz Ronaldo', 'Pele', 'Diego Maradona', 'NesCafe'],
    correct_option: 'Pele'
  },
  {
    question: `Which country's team was the first in the history of soccer to win the highest title - world champion?`,
    options: ['Brazil', 'Uruguay', 'Argentina', 'USSR'],
    correct_option: 'Uruguay'
  },
  {
    question: 'In what year was the first world soccer championship held?',
    options: ['1970', '1980', '2000', '1930'],
    correct_option: '1930'
  },
  {
    question: "Which country's national team did the legendary footballer Diego Maradona play for?",
    options: ['Brazil', 'Argentina', 'Uruguay', 'Russia'],
    correct_option: 'Argentina'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the home country of soccer?',
    options: ['USA', 'England', 'Holland', 'Germany'],
    correct_option: 'England'
  },
  {
    question: "Which country's team won the World Cup title in 2014?",
    options: ['Germany', 'Russia', 'Brazil', 'Portugal'],
    correct_option: 'Germany'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the weight of the lightest soccer boots?',
    options: ['80 grams', '99 grams', '127 grams', '153 grams'],
    correct_option: '99 grams'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who officiates an official soccer match?',
    options: ['The spectators', 'The head coach', 'The referee', 'Members of the state commission'],
    correct_option: 'The referee'
  },
  {
    question: 'What does the referee mean when showing players a yellow card?',
    options: ['A warning', 'Replacing a player', 'Nothing', 'A penalty'],
    correct_option: 'A warning'
  },
  {
    question: `Which team's player scored the fastest goal in World Cup history?`,
    options: ['Spain', 'England', 'Denmark', 'Turkey'],
    correct_option: 'Turkey'
  },
  {
    question: 'The location of the first world soccer tournament?',
    options: ['Moscow (USSR)', 'Leningrad (USSR)', 'Motevideo (Uruguay)', 'Buenos Aires (Argentina)'],
    correct_option: 'Motevideo (Uruguay)'
  }
];
